Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 4: Boxes 192-256
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 4: Boxes 192-256
- Amalgamated Lithographers of America, Publication (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Good and bad unionism, 1951-1957 (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Talks continue in Western Strike, 1951-1957 (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Bindery union asked at Western, 1951-1957 (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Industry covered by pension set-up, 1951-1957 (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Labor boosts automation, 1951-1957 (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Western strike continues meeting yields no settlement, 1951-1957 (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Mediator, union confer on strike of Lithographers, 1951-1957 (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Co. cites normal operations, 1951-1957 (Box 234, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Lithographers of America, Publication (Box 234, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Directory of union label Lithographers, 1959; Publication (Box 234, Folder 2)
    Author: Amalgamated Lithographers of America
  - Item 2: Directory of union label Lithographers, 1966; Publication (Box 234, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Addresses of the Officers, 1949; Publication (Box 234, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Lithographers of America, Publication (Box 234, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: San Francisco Lithographers: Pension plan, 1950; Publication (Box 234, Folder 3)
    Author: San Francisco Lithographers
  - Item 2: Employees benefit plan, Publication (Box 234, Folder 3)
    Author: American Newspaper Guild
  - Item 3: Cleveland Union Lithographers Health and Welfare Fund, Publication (Box 234, Folder 3)
    Author: Lithographers and Photengravers International Union. Local No. 6-L (Cleveland, Ohio)
  - Item 4: Pension and benefit plans: recommended for the consideration of the membership of Local 1 by the Trustees of the Health, Welfare and Pension Fund, Publication (Box 234, Folder 3)
    Author: Amalgamated Lithographers of America. Local 1 (New York)
  - Item 5: Press Release - April 2, 1951, Publication (Box 234, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Lithographers of America, Publication (Box 234, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Lithographers Journal, 1950; Publication (Box 234, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: 75 years of Lithographic Progress1882-1957, Publication (Box 234, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Lithographers of America, Publication (Box 234, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The agreement to merge, 1963; Publication (Box 234, Folder 5)
    Author: Amalgamated Lithographers of America; International Photo Engravers Union
- Amalgamated Lithographers of America, Publication (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Annual Report (6th), 1956; Publication (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Annual Report (7th), 1957; Publication (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Annual Report (8th), 1958; Publication (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Annual Report (10th), 1960; Publication (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Official referendum ballotamendments to the Trust Indenture of the Inter-Local Pension Fund, 1956; Publication (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: The Golden years, Publication (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Help organize, Publication (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Have your say the Union way attend meetings!, Publication (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Welcome to ALA, Publication (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: For better pay go ALA, Publication (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Go all the way with ALA, Publication (Box 235, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Lithographers of America, Publication (Box 235, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Art is not an end in itself, but a means of addressing humanity, 1962; Publication (Box 235, Folder 2)
    Notes: New York Times, Sept. 30, 1962, Section II, Advertisement
  - Item 2: Facts you should know about the Amalgamated Lithographers of America, 1950; Publication (Box 235, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Here's a labor union that pushes for more labor-saving devices, 1956; Publication (Box 235, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Lithographers of America, Publication (Box 235, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Lithographers' Union Story, 1926-1927 (Box 235, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: The Story of American Lithographers, 1940; Publication (Box 235, Folder 3)
    Notes: Supplement to the Lithographers' Journal, March, 1940, vol. xxiv, No. 12
- Amalgamated Lithographers of America, Publication (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: correspondence, 1960; Publication (Box 235, Folder 4)
    Author: Labor's Committee for the Election of Kennedy and Johnson
  - Item 2: Art is not an end in itself, but a means of addressing humanity, 1962; Publication (Box 235, Folder 4)
    Notes: New York Times, Sept. 30, 1962, Section II, Advertisement. Copy 2
  - Item 3: Bulletin, 1954; Publication (Box 235, Folder 4)
    Author: Printing Industry of America
    Notes: vol.7:no.49
  - Item 4: Bulletin, 1954; Publication (Box 235, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol.8:no.4
  - Item 5: Always looking ahead, Publication (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Lithographers Attention!!, Publication (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Feather in this cap, Publication (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Good and bad unionism, Publication (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: This union label, Publication (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Labor boosts automation, Publication (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Executives attend unions school, Publication (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Cites Lithographers' Union as clean, idealistic, Publication (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Offset is lithography, Publication (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Here's a labor union that pushes for more labor-saving devices, Publication (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Concerning Lithography and Lithographic Workers, 1944; Publication (Box 235, Folder 4)
    Notes: Articles about Offset/Lithography
  - Item 16: Offset is Lithography, Publication (Box 235, Folder 4)
    Notes: Pamphlet explaining Lithography. 2 copies
  - Item 17: The appropriate bargaining union for Lithographic Production Employees, 1966; Publication (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: National pattern standards of apprenticeship and training in the Lithographic Industry, 1958; Publication (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: The Changing look in "Litho, U.S.A.", Publication (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: A tradition of craftsmanship, 1963; Publication (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: A tradition of craftsmanship, 1966; Publication (Box 235, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Lithographers of America, Publication (Box 235, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Handbook for organizers: 75 years of progress, 1957; Publication (Box 235, Folder 5)
    Author: Amalgamated Lithographers of America.
  - Item 2: Sample organizing campaign letters, Publication (Box 235, Folder 5)
- BLE (Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers), Publication (Box 236, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: copy of Group Policy Contract No. 22000-G, 1964; Publication (Box 236, Folder 1)
    Author: Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (U.S.)
  - Item 2: Group Insurance Plan, negotiated for railroad employees, 1964; Publication (Box 236, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Group Insurance Program for retired members of the Brotherhood, 1964; Publication (Box 236, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Group Insurance Program for employees not in active service who are members of the Brotherhood, 1964; Publication (Box 236, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: The Health and Welfare Plan of the Nation's Railroads and the Railway Labor Organizationsgroup policy contract GA-23000., 1977; Publication (Box 236, Folder 1)
- BLE (Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers), Publication (Box 236, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: BLE Centennial/GIA Diamond Jubilee, Detroit, Michigan, May 5-8, 1963, Publication (Box 236, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: A brief history of the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1977; Publication (Box 236, Folder 2)
    Author: Richard J. Cook
- BLE (Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers), Publication (Box 236, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Injured railroad workers: know your rights: a brief outline of railroad workers' rights under the Federal Employers' Liability Act: how to protect them, 1956; Publication (Box 236, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Let's stop this billion dollar washout before it starts!, Publication (Box 236, Folder 3)
- BLE (Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers), Publication (Box 236, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Minutes/proceedings of meeting held Dec. 7, 1931, Publication (Box 236, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Calendar from 1968, Publication (Box 236, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Radio Broadcast - "Let's think about it" - Feb. 5, 1951", Publication (Box 236, Folder 4)
    Author: Basil Reuss
  - Item 4: Are you aware? An overview of some rights and obligations of a BLE member and some procedures under the Railway Labor Act, rate yourself, 1977; Publication (Box 236, Folder 4)
- BLE (Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers), Publication (Box 236, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Selected awards of the First Division, National Railroad Adjustment Board on investigation and discipline procedures, 1974; Publication (Box 236, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Guide for preparation and distribution of submissions to National Railroad Adjustment Board, First Division, 1974; Publication (Box 236, Folder 5)
    Notes: Revised July 1, 1974
  - Item 3: article - 200,000 scapegoats, 1962; Publication (Box 236, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Advertisement, 1963; Publication (Box 236, Folder 5)
    Notes: New York Times, May 5, 1963, Section 11
  - Item 5: copy of Public Law 93-445, 93rd Congress, H.R. 15301, 1974; Publication (Box 236, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Rail Engineers' Chief outlines "Crusade for 60's", Publication (Box 236, Folder 5)
    Author: BLE Public Relations Dept.
  - Item 7: Correspondence To the Shipping and Traveling Public (Cleveland, Ohio), 1962; Publication (Box 236, Folder 5)
    Notes: 1962 July 9
  - Item 8: The Case for Locomotive helpers (Firemen), 1963; Publication (Box 236, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Railway Labor Organizations National Group Insurance Plan. Contract GA-23000, 1972; Publication (Box 236, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Crusade for the 60's, 1965; Publication (Box 236, Folder 5)
    Author: Perry S. Heath
  - Item 11: Dissent to report of the Presidential Railroad Commission, 1962; Publication (Box 236, Folder 5)
    Author: A. F. Zimmerman
  - Item 12: Inside railroading: the work-rules dispute, 1961; Publication (Box 236, Folder 5)
- BLE (Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers), Publication (Box 236, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Guide for Secretary-Treasurers, Local Divisions, Publication (Box 236, Folder 6)
- BLE (Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers), Publication (Box 236, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Crusade for the 60's, 1965; Publication (Box 236, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: BLE Centennial/GIA Diamond Jubilee, Detroit, Michigan, May 5-8, 1963, Publication (Box 236, Folder 7)
    Notes: Souvenir program. Copy 2
- BLE (Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers), Publication (Box 236, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: I am a Locomotive Engineer, Prime mover-producer of Railroad Transportation Services in quality and quantity for America, 1977; Publication (Box 236, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: You are there!, 1961; Publication (Box 236, Folder 8)
    Notes: Script for play
  - Item 3: Grievance procedure at the local level, 1979; Publication (Box 236, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Due process: a manual for use in providing representation to employees involved in discipline and dismissal cases, 1980; Publication (Box 236, Folder 8)
- BLE (Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers), Publication (Box 236, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Convention Manual - 6th Biennial Meeting, 1956; Publication (Box 236, Folder 9)
- Loyal Legions of Loggers and Lumbermen, Publication (Box 237, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Conference and Co-operation: questions and answers, 1924; Publication (Box 237, Folder 1)
    Author: Loyal Legions of Loggers and Lumbermen
- ILA (International Longshoremen's Association), Publication (Box 237, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Sun turns light on Mob rule on docks, 1948-1956 (Box 237, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: CIO to reorganize red-controlled unions, 1948-1956 (Box 237, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Coast-wide pact Chief ILA aim, 1948-1956 (Box 237, Folder 2)
- National Longshoremen's Board, Publication (Box 237, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: In the matter of the Arbitration between Pacific Coast District Local 38 of the Internat'l. Longshoremen's Assoc., 1934; Publication (Box 237, Folder 3)
    Author: National Longshoremen's Board
    Notes: Arbitration
  - Item 2: Jobless Longshoremen in NY get special training in new program by employers, dock labor union, 1981; Publication (Box 237, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: arbitration - between - Internat'l. Longshoremen's Assoc. and NY Shipping Assoc., 1958; Publication (Box 237, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: arbitration - between - NY Shipping Assoc and International Longshoremen's Assoc and the Atlantic Coast District Wage Scale, 1947; Publication (Box 237, Folder 3)
    Notes: Arbitration 2 copies
  - Item 5: International Longshoremen's Assoc. and American Molasses Company, 1940; Publication (Box 237, Folder 3)
    Notes: Arbitration decision
- ILA (International Longshoremen's Association), Publication (Box 237, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Directory, 1936-1937 (Box 237, Folder 4)
    Author: International Longshoremen's Association
  - Item 2: Directory, 1964-1965 (Box 237, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: The Longshoremen's Voice, 1967; Publication (Box 237, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol.1:no.1-2 (1967)
- ILA (International Longshoremen's Association), Publication (Box 237, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Voice of 856, 1955-1956 (Box 237, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.1:no.1-12, 14-30, 32-47, 49. 2 copies
- International Longshoremen's Association, Publication (Box 238, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Brooklyn Longshoreman, 1968-1978 (Box 238, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol. 16, no.2-5 (1976); Aug. 1978 Special Merger Issue; vol. 17, no. 1 (1977); vol.8, no. 1,4-5 (1968); vol.9, no.1,3-5 (1969); vol.10, no.2,5-6 (1970); vol.11, no.2-5 (1971)
- International Longshoremen's Association, Publication (Box 238, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Brooklyn Longshoreman, 1972-1976 (Box 238, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol. 12, no.3-5 (1972); vol. 13, no.1-6 (1973); vol. 14, no.1-2,4 (1974); vol. 15, no.1, 3-4 (1975); vol. 16, no.1 (1976)
- International Longshoremen's Association, Publication (Box 238, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Brooklyn Longshoreman, 1964-1968 (Box 238, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. 8, no.2 (1968); vol.7, no.6, 8-10 (1967); vol.6, no. 1-11 (1966); vol.5, no.1-10 (1965); vol. 4, no.3-12 (1964)
- International Longshoremen's Association, Publication (Box 238, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Brooklyn Longshoreman, 1967-1972 (Box 238, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 12, no.1-2 (1972); vol.11, no.1,6 (1971); vol.10, no.1,3-4,7 (1970); vol.9, no.2, 6-7 (1969); vol.7, no.1-4 (1967)
  - Item 2: Brooklyn Longshoremen's Center - Report (1965), Publication (Box 238, Folder 4)
- International Longshoremen's Association, Publication (Box 238, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: To: All ILA Members in the Port of New York, From: The ILA Executive Council and the Entire Negotiating Committee, 1965; Publication (Box 238, Folder 5)
- International Longshoremen's Association, Publication (Box 238, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Draft of a bill to provide Federal Workmen's Compensation for the protection of Interstate Commerce and Harbor Workers, 1926; Publication (Box 238, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Petition of the Longshoremen of the United States., 1935; Publication (Box 238, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Before the National War Labor Board, Publication (Box 238, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Pacific Coast Longshoremen's Strike of 1934, Publication (Box 238, Folder 6)
    Author: Herman Phleger
  - Item 5: The strike as I have seen it, 1934; Publication (Box 238, Folder 6)
    Author: George Percy Hedley
  - Item 6: The San Francisco strike as I have seen it, 1934; Publication (Box 238, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: The New Orleans Longshoremen (reprinted from Political Science Quarterly, vol. LVII, no.4, Dec. 1942), Publication (Box 238, Folder 6)
    Author: Herbert R. Northrup
- International Longshoremen's Association, Publication (Box 238, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Brooklyn Longshoremen's Center - Report (1965), Publication (Box 238, Folder 7)
    Notes: second copy
  - Item 2: Unionism and democracy in the Merchant Marine, Publication (Box 238, Folder 7)
    Notes: flyer
  - Item 3: 8th Annual Report (1966), Publication (Box 238, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Press Release - Open letter to the American famer which acknowledges the mass of communications on the Russian Grain Sales, 1975; Publication (Box 238, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: A contemporary analysis of a labor union, 1966; Publication (Box 238, Folder 7)
- International Longshoremen's Association, Publication (Box 238, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Pension Book of the NYSA-ILA Pension Trust Fund, 1957; Publication (Box 238, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Safety rules for the prevention of accidents to Longshoremen, 1929; Publication (Box 238, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Texas Ports Maritime Safety Rules, 1929; Publication (Box 238, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Your welfare fund, 1956; Publication (Box 238, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Your Benefit Plan, 1956; Publication (Box 238, Folder 8)
- International Longshoremen's Association, Publication (Box 238, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Health vs. Relief, Publication (Box 238, Folder 9)
    Notes: article
  - Item 2: Union member's handbook, 1964; Publication (Box 238, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Press release - from Thomas W. Gleason, International Pres. Of the Executive Council of the AFL-CIO, 1975; Publication (Box 238, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: A story of Service (brochure/advertisement for the Medical Center), 1964; Publication (Box 238, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: The Maritime crisis: what is and what it isn't, 1936; Publication (Box 238, Folder 9)
- International Longshoremen's Association, Publication (Box 239, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Pacific Coast Longshoremen's Strike of 1934, Publication (Box 239, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Information and union comment on the 1960 Mechanization and Modernization fund agreement between The Longshoremen of the Pacific Coast and The Steamship and Stevedoring Employers, Publication (Box 239, Folder 1)
- International Longshoremen's Association, Publication (Box 239, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: one letter to 'All ILWU Locals, District Councils and Auxiliaries' from the International Longshoremen's & Warehousemen's Union. Regarding voting problems on - Repeal of the Poll Tax, Extension of voting rights, Against repeal of ret subsidies in the Omn, 1966; Publication (Box 239, Folder 2)
    Notes: Correspondence
- International Longshoremen's Association, Publication (Box 239, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Portrait of a leader, 1952; Publication (Box 239, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: The Innocents, 1952; Publication (Box 239, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Piracy and Pillage, 1952; Publication (Box 239, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: A Plaque for Joe, 1952; Publication (Box 239, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: The Silent, 1952; Publication (Box 239, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: The Reformer, 1952; Publication (Box 239, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: The Terrorist, 1952; Publication (Box 239, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: The Victim, 1952; Publication (Box 239, Folder 3)
- International Brotherhood of Longshoremen, Publication (Box 240, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: IBL Reporter, 1955-1956 (Box 240, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.1, no.1-5; vol.2, no.1-5
- International Brotherhood of Longshoremen, Publication (Box 240, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Longshoreman's work record, 1955-1956 (Box 240, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: correspondence, 1956; Publication (Box 240, Folder 2)
- International Brotherhood of Longshoremen, Publication (Box 240, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Longshoremen's Journal - 'Launching Number' and 1937, Publication (Box 240, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Longshoremen's Journal - 1937, Publication (Box 240, Folder 3)
- International Brotherhood of Longshoremen, Publication (Box 240, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Longshoremen's Journal - 1929, 1939; Publication (Box 240, Folder 4)
- AFL-ILA for Checkers, Clerks and Timekeepers, Publication (Box 240, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Tally, 1954; Publication (Box 240, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.1, no. 16, 18
- IBL Longshore Committee, Publication (Box 240, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Waterfront News, 1956-1959 (Box 240, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.5, no.1-9, 11; vol.4, no.1-6, 8-12; vol.3, no.13,27-49, 51-52; vol.2, no.16,18,20,22,25,27,29
- IBL Longshore Committee, Publication (Box 240, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Waterfront News, 1956-1959 (Box 240, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.5,no.1-10; vol.3, no.1-5,26-29; vol.2, no.47-48- 52
- IBL Longshore Committee, Publication (Box 240, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Waterfront News, 1958; Publication (Box 240, Folder 8)
    Notes: vol.3, no.7-9,11-20,22-25,30- 46,48-50; vol.4, no.14-12
- IBL Longshore Committee, Publication (Box 240, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Waterfront News, 1955-1958 (Box 240, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol.3, no.42,45-52; vol.4, no.1-6,8-12; vol.2, no.16- 18,20-36,38-46
- IBL Longshore Committee, Publication (Box 240, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Waterfront News, 1954-1955 (Box 240, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol.1, no.41-47,49-52- special issues from 1954- 1955
- IBL Longshore Committee, Publication (Box 240, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Waterfront News, 1955-1958 (Box 240, Folder 11)
    Notes: vol.2, no.1-2,4-11,13-15; vol.1, no.39-51; vol.2, no.1- 2,4-15
- International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union (ILWU)., Publication (Box 240, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Types of American labor unions, 1905; Publication (Box 240, Folder 12)
    Author: John Rogers Commons
- International Longshoremen's Association, Publication (Box 241, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Transcript of speech - Remarks by Thomas W. Gleason, Pres., International Longshoremen's Associationat the Third Annual Joint Congressional Breakfast, Washington, DC (Feb. 26, 1969), Publication (Box 241, Folder 1)
    Author: Thomas W. Gleason
- International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union (ILWU)., Publication (Box 241, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The 'Penalty Awards' of Irvin Stalmaster, 1939; Publication (Box 241, Folder 2)
    Author: Irvin Stalmaster
  - Item 2: In re labor dispute between Ahukini Terminal Company, Ltd., Castle & Cooke Terminals, Ltd., Hilo Transportation & Terminal Company, Ltd., Kahului Railroad Company, Kauai Terminals, Ltd., Mahukona Terminals, Ltd., and McCabe, Hamilton and Renny Co., Ltd. a, 1949; Publication (Box 241, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: In arbitration proceedings pursuant to Article E, paragraph no. 56, of Amendment dated October 18, 1960 to Pacific Coast Longshore Agreement: in the matter of a controversy between International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, Complainant, and, 1961; Publication (Box 241, Folder 2)
- International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union (ILWU)., Publication (Box 241, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Pension plan for Stevedores and Wharf Clerks, 1961; Publication (Box 241, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Outline of ILWU-PMA Benefits Funds, Welfare and Retirement Plans, 1965; Publication (Box 241, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Pineapple Medical Plan, 1959; Publication (Box 241, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Hawaii ILWU Leader's Handbook of Services, Benefits., 1969; Publication (Box 241, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Medical Plan (1961-1963) (Box 241, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Summary plan description ILWU-PMA, Welfare Plan, 1977; Publication (Box 241, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Welfare and Retirement Programs: An outline, 1973; Publication (Box 241, Folder 3)
- International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union (ILWU), Publication (Box 241, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Hawaii ILWU Leader's handbook of Services., 1972; Publication (Box 241, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: The meaning of $149,000,000 (Trustees Report), 1965; Publication (Box 241, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Welfare & pensions on the docks of the Pacific coast, 1956; Publication (Box 241, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Pensions on the waterfront, 1952; Publication (Box 241, Folder 4)
- International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union (ILWU). Local 142, Publication (Box 241, Folder 5)